Andrii Tykhoniuk

Front-end Developer





Hello! I'm from Ukraine. Now I am in Wroclaw. I have been living here for 3 years. I'm a professional results-oriented Front-end developer, with a successful record of cross-browser semantic adaptive layout. Flexibility is one of my main features that is why I can adapt to any working conditions. I have more than 2 years of experience, creating work using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REACT, REDUX, TypeScript, Bootstrap and Docker. So, I think I could be useful to you in achieving your company's goals. I am a quiet, active, open, and motivated individual, due to my strong analytical and critical thinking I can find simple solutions to complex problems. I have a high level of self-organization and self-development. I know how to find a common language with different people, and I am not afraid to take responsibility. I believe that our whole life is a constant continuous development, where our attention, there's our energy, and that in our life increases. Therefore I made my choice.

SKILLS

- Technologies: HTML, CSS, SASS/SCSS/LESS, AJAX, AXIOS, REACT, REDUX, API, FORMIK, REDUX-THUNK, REDUX-TOOLKIT, REACT-ROUTER
- Tools: WEBPACK, GULP, GIT, NPM, PHOTOSHOP, FIGMA, DEVTOOLS, JQUERY, DOCKER, NAKAMA
- CSS methodologies: BEM
- UI frameworks: BOOTSTRAP, MATERIAL
- Programming languages: JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT, PHP
- Languages: POLISH, UKRAINIAN, RUSSIAN, ENGLISH (Intermediate)

EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2022

Personal Assistant

STABILBAU SP. Z O.O

Responsibilities:

marketing, employment, recruiting, people, and project management

2020 - 2022

Freelancer

Front-end Developer

Responsibilities:

creating responsive websites and applications

Front-end Developer

CC GAMES SP Z O.O

Responsibilities:

creating responsive websites and applications, development of Arena

Tournament using (JS, React, TypeScript, Redux, PHP, Docker, and Nakama)

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

Master's degree, Automation, and Computer-integrated Technologies

2022

Udemy, Full course in JavaScript + React - from beginner to results by Ivan Petrychenko

Front-end Developer

Certificates:

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-b32bdeb3-2fa4-4ea9-a415-ffc8d06b8f9b/

2022

Udemy, WEB - developer by Ivan Petrychenko

Front-end Developer

Certificates:

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-1ec539ea-9582-4ed3-829f-1c719823c207/

2022

Udemy, Practical Java Script (advanced level) by Ivan Petrychenko

Front-end Developer

Certificates:

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ff86bec6-b429-45ec-83a0-8c0bd5476529/

2023

Udemy, Full course on modern TypeScript by Ivan Petrychenko

Front-end Developer

Certificates:

_

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO

individual project

Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, React-router-dom, Styled-components, Swiper js

Tools: Webpack, NPM, Git

Link: https://react-portfolio-gamma-khaki.vercel.app/#/

Source: https://github.com/AndrewTihonyuk878/react-portfolio

CHESS-REACT

individual project

Technologies: HTML, SCSS, JS, REACT, TypeScript, Redux

Tools: Webpack, NPM, Git, DevTools, Figma **Link:** https://react-chess-ecru.vercel.app/

Source: https://github.com/AndrewTihonyuk878/react-chess

REACT-PIZZA

individual project

Technologies: HTML, SCSS, REACT, TypeScript, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, AXIOS, MockApi, React-router-dom

Tools: Webpack, NPM, Git, DevTools, Figma **Link:** https://react-pizza-brown.vercel.app/

Source: https://github.com/AndrewTihonyuk878/react-pizza

EMPLOYEES DATA ARRANGEMENT (EDA) WEB APP

individual project

Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, React-router-dom

Tools: Webpack, NPM, Git

Link: https://employers-one.vercel.app/

Source: https://github.com/AndrewTihonyuk878/employers

MARVELSERVICE

individual project

Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Marvel API, React-router-dom

Tools: Webpack, NPM, Git

Link: https://marvel-starter-react-hooks.vercel.app/

Source: https://github.com/AndrewTihonyuk878/marvel_starter_react_hooks

... more in my portfolio.